http://www.colmetsb.com/privacy.html

We Are NowRTT Engineered Solutions
If you are not automatically redirected after a few seconds, just click anywhere.
Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions Website Privacy Statement 1. Acknowledgment and Acceptance of Terms Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions, you acknowledge and fully understand Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions’s Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement. 2. Participating Merchant Policies Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties. 2a. Use of the services of this Site is restricted to individuals who can enter into legally enforceable agreements under applicable law. Please do not use this Site if you are a minor or are otherwise incapable of entering into a legally binding agreement. 3. Information We Collect and How We Use It Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from our Web Server logs, the user, and with Cookies. a. Web Server Logs. When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:
Your Internet protocol address. The kind of browser or computer you use. Number of links you click within the site. State or country from which you accessed the site. Date and time of your visit. Name of your Internet service provider. Web page you linked to our site from. Pages you viewed on the site.
b. Use of Cookies Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality. Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, but does not allow other companies to place cookies on our website unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value (such as merging into Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions.com a site that relies on third-party cookies). You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website. Personal Information Users We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:
To fulfill your service requests for services. To protect ourselves from liability. To respond to legal process or comply with law, or In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.
4. Use of Web Beacons or Gif Files Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons – sometimes also called single-pixel gifs – that allow Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site. Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information. 5. Accessing Web Account Information We will provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in your web account file is correct and current. You may review this information by contacting us by sending an email to our support attendant at: info@colmetsb.com 6. Changes to This Statement Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the “updated” date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates. 7. Contacting Us If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us at: info@colmetsb.com or send your comments to: Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions Attention: Privacy Statement Personnel
Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions
2975 Discovery Blvd. Rockwall, Texas 75032
Toll Free: 888-452-6684 Phone: 972-772-1919 eFax: 972-408-0881 sales@colmetsb.com
Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.
INTRODUCING COL-MET'S NEW PRODUCT INNOVATION
Request For Information
Paint Booths
Powder Booths
Ovens
Air Makeup Units
Preparation Equipment
Accessories
News & Press
Josh Woyame joins Col-Met as Eastern Regional Sales Manager July 8, 2019 Rockwall, TX, July 8, 2019…… Col-Met is pleased to announce Josh Woyame has joined Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions as Eastern Regional Sales Manager effective July 1, 2019.  Josh joins the Col-Met team with 20-years of experience in... Read More Read More
Judy Lietzke to join Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions as Marketing Manager April 22, 2019 Col-Met is pleased to announce Judy Lietzke will join Col-Met Engineered Finishing Solutions as Marketing Manager effective April 29, 2019.  Judy joins the Col-Met team with a tremendous amount of experience in marketing related to the finishing... Read More Read More
Col-Met New 5-Year Warranty Program - Effective February 1 February 1, 2019 Col-Met is extremely excited to announce our 5-Year Warranty Program, effective February 1, 2019! The quality and workmanship of Col-Met spray booths allows us to be the only Spray... Read More Read More
View All News
Events
View All Events
Col-Met products can be designed to meet with OSHA and NFPA regulations. Copyright ©2020 Col-Met EFS | All right reserved | Privacy | Digital Marketing
